Ethan Holen

COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY CLASS OF 2022, B.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE

□720-326-5046 | Sethanholen@gmail.com | #6 ethanholen.com | GethanHolen | Gethanholen-563856174

Sum**marv**

Current research assistant, and undergraduate at Colorado State University with experience in both the software and hardware side of the tech industry. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys backpacking, mountain biking and camping in the mountains of Colorado. Interested in gaining new and interesting experiences in the field of software development.

Experience

CSU - Natural User Interaction Lab

Fort Collins CO

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

May. 2020 - Present

- Currently working as a research assistant with CSU's NUILab
- Designing virtual and augmented reality environments for Research projects
- · Technologies: Unity, C#

IOS Development Denver CO

IOS DEVELOPER FOR DCSO AND MAYO CLINIC

July. 2019 - Present

- Currently working with Mayo clinic to design a custom vaccine App for patient care
- Wrote custom IOS Application for Douglas County Sheriffs Office
- Designed and Created a secure back-end using AWS Lambda and API Gateway
- Technologies: Swift, Xcode, AWS Lambda, API Gateway

Valor Christian High School

Highlands Ranch, CO.

Aug. 2016 - May. 2018

May. 2016 - Jul. 2016

IT INTERN

- Provided hardware and software solutions for help desk tickets
- Helped manage a JAMF environment of 550 Apple devices
- Setup and management of 20 Aerohive network access points

Express Care Cheyenne, WY

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

- Assisted Doctor or PA on call as a scribe
- · Vitals and initial patient charts, Strep, urine and vision tests

Education

COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY(COLLEGE OF NATURAL SCIENCES)

Fort Collins, CO

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

Relevant Coursework: Intro to Java Programming (Java), Data Structures (Java),
 Computer Organization (C/C++), OS and Networks (Bash), Discrete Structures and their Applications (Python),
 Managing Big Data (Python), Operating Systems (C), Software Development (C++)

Valor Christian High School

Highlands Ranch, CO Aug. 2014 - May. 2018

Feb 22-23

Aug. 2017

• Relevant Coursework: AP Computer Science (Java), Web Design (HTML/CSS)

Other

HackCU VI (4th Place)

Boulder, CO

• Wrote angular front end for an easy to use API creation tool.

 $\bullet \ \ \text{Won fourth place overall in the competition. Details: https://devpost.com/software/backend-rzdbu3}$

Languages & Technologies

PERSONAL

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

- Programming Languages: Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Bash, Swift, C, C++, C#
- Software: OSX, Windows, Linux, AWS, Xcode, Personal Website, Unity

Medical Missions Work Ethiopia

A solist and independent of the solistic services and baseline and tracts

• Assisted physicians with scribe work and basic medical tests.

Video: https://govalor.com/discovery-ethiopia-video/

Eagle Scout - Troop 102Patrol Leader, Troop Historian

Greenwood Village, CO

Sep. 2011 - May. 2015

• Learned Leadership and organization through positions of patrol leader and troop historian

Project: Built a garden and fence around the local Orthodox monastery